efin.cx 2019-03-31

# Privacy Policy

### Basic Information

When you visit the website or use our services or application, we collect information sent to us by your computer, mobile phone, or other access device. This information may include your IP address, device information including, but not limited to, identifier, name and type, operating system, location, mobile network information and standard web log information, such as your browser type, traffic to and from our site and the pages you accessed on our website.

If you create an account or use our services, we may collect the following types of information:

  * Contact information - your name, address, phone, email, Skype ID and other similar information.

When you use our services, we collect information about your transactions and your other activities on our website and we may collect information about your computer or other access device for fraud prevention purposes.

In order to help protect you from fraud and misuse of your personal information, we may collect information about your use and interaction with our website or services. For example, we may evaluate your computer, mobile phone or other access device to identify any malicious software or activity that may affect the availability of our services.

Finally, we may collect additional information from or about you in other ways such as contacts with our customer support team.

### How We Use Cookies

When you access our website or content or use our application or services, we or companies we work with may place small data files called cookies or pixel tags on your computer or other device. We use these technologies to: 

  * Recognize you as a customer;
  * Customize services;
  * Measure promotional effectiveness; and
  * Collect information about your computer or other access device to mitigate risk, help prevent fraud and promote trust and safety.

We use both session and persistent cookies when you access our website or content. Session cookies expire and no longer have any effect when you log out of your account or close your browser. Persistent cookies remain on your browser until you erase them or they expire.

We also use Local Shared Objects, commonly referred to as “Flash cookies,” to help ensure that your account security is not compromised, to spot irregularities in behavior to help prevent fraud and to support our sites and services.

We encode our cookies so that only we can interpret the information stored in them. You are free to decline our cookies if your browser or browser add-on permits, but doing so may interfere with your use of our website. The help section of most browsers or browser add-ons provides instructions on blocking, deleting or disabling cookies.

You may encounter our cookies or pixel tags on websites that we do not control. For example, if you view a web page created by a third party or use an application developed by a third party, there may be a cookie or pixel tag placed by the web page or application. Likewise, these third parties may place cookies or pixel tags that are not subject to our control and the Privacy Policy does not cover their use.

### How We Protect And Store Personal Information

Throughout this policy, we use the term "personal information" to describe information that can be associated with a specific person and can be used to identify that person. We do not consider personal information to include information that has been anonymized so that it does not identify a specific user.

We store and process your personal information by maintaining physical, electronic and procedural safeguards in compliance with applicable regulations.

### How We Use Personal Information We Collect

Our primary purpose in collecting personal information is to provide you with a secure, smooth, efficient, and customized experience. We may use your personal information to:

  * Provide services and customer support you request;
  * Process transactions and send notices about your transactions;
  * Resolve disputes, collect fees, and troubleshoot problems;
  * Prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities;
  * Customize, measure, and improve services and the content and layout of our website and applications;
  * Deliver targeted marketing, service update notices, and promotional offers based on your communication preferences;
